International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Records 5432
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Brotherhood of Pulp Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Records
1906-1957
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers
5432
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Records consisting of the President-Secretary files for the years 1906-1957.
5650548
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 08, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 12, 2019
Scope and Contents
The International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Records consist largely of the President-Secretary files for the years 1906-1957. They are arranged for microfilming and indexed first by the year then by category.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5097: New York State Board of Mediation and Arbitration Transcripts and Exhibits 5288: International Brotherhood Pulp, Sulphite, Paper Mill Workers, Local 670 (Utica, NY) Minute Book 5432 mf: International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers Records on Microfilm 6030: Archival Collective Bargaining Agreements File 6046: Archives Union File (AUF)
Paper industry workers x Labor unions z United States.; Collective bargaining x Paper industry z United States.; International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers.
5650548
- President-Secretary files: cross index directory, 1906-1916 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- President-Secretary files: cross index directory, 1917-1922 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- President-Secretary files: cross index directory, 1923-1928 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- President-Secretary files, 1906-1916 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- President-Secretary files, 1917-1922 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- President-Secretary files, 1923-1928 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- President-Secretary files, 1929-1934 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- President-Secretary files, 1935-1938 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- President-Secretary files, 1939-1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- President-Secretary files, 1942-1944 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- President-Secretary files, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- President-Secretary files, 1947-1949 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- President-Secretary files, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- President-Secretary files, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- President-Secretary files, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- President-Secretary files, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 16)